[{"answer": " Hello", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Hey, its Paul", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Hello", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Paul, I havent heard from you in a long time.  Hows it going", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Hey, its Paul", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Good.  Im just going to school and playing baseball.  Hows college life", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Paul, I havent heard from you in a long time.  Hows it going", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Its going great.  Classes are pretty good, and we have a break next week.  I", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Good.  Im just going to school and playing baseball.  Hows college life", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " No, not really.  Thats kind of why I called", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Its going great.  Classes are pretty good, and we have a break next week.  I", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Whats going on with it", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 23, "question": " No, not really.  Thats kind of why I called", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Well, I just dont know where to start.  I know I need to apply soon, but I don", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Whats going on with it", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Yeah, the process can be a little overwhelming.  But, you just need to take i", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Well, I just dont know where to start.  I know I need to apply soon, but I don", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Can you help me?  What should I do first", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Yeah, the process can be a little overwhelming.  But, you just need to take i", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " The first thing you need to do is pick the schools you want to apply to.  Hav", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Can you help me?  What should I do first", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " No.  I dont know how to decide.  There are thousands of schools to choose from", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 40, "question": " The first thing you need to do is pick the schools you want to apply to.  Hav", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Schools can be really competitive these days.  So, I think you should apply t", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 44, "question": " No.  I dont know how to decide.  There are thousands of schools to choose from", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Thats a lot", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Schools can be really competitive these days.  So, I think you should apply t", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " I know it sounds like a lot, but its a good idea to apply for many schools", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Thats a lot", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 51, "question": " I know it sounds like a lot, but its a good idea to apply for many schools", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Now, you should apply to all different kinds of schools too", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 52, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " What do you mean", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Now, you should apply to all different kinds of schools too", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " I mean, you should apply to some really good schools that are hard to get int", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 54, "question": " What do you mean", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Why", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 59, "question": " I mean, you should apply to some really good schools that are hard to get int", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Because if you only apply to the top schools in the nation, like say the top five", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Why", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " OK.  I see.  Is there anything else I should think about while applying", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Because if you only apply to the top schools in the nation, like say the top five", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Sure.  There are lots of things. Youll need to go to each universitys websit", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 65, "question": " OK.  I see.  Is there anything else I should think about while applying", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Is it the same for most schools", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Sure.  There are lots of things. Youll need to go to each universitys websit", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": "The basic application materials are usually the same, but different school", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Is it the same for most schools", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " When should I apply", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 78, "question": "The basic application materials are usually the same, but different school", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " Thats something else you can check on at the schools website.  The deadline", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 79, "question": " When should I apply", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " I guess I should start on it now", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 83, "question": " Thats something else you can check on at the schools website.  The deadline", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Yeah.  Usually you have to send in your application materials by December fo", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 84, "question": " I guess I should start on it now", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Thats early.  Id better start already", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 88, "question": " Yeah.  Usually you have to send in your application materials by December fo", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " You need to.  Why dont you do some research into what schools you want t", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 89, "question": " Thats early.  Id better start already", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " OK, I will", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 93, "question": " You need to.  Why dont you do some research into what schools you want t", "qSentId": 92},{"answer": " Ill help you along the way since Ive already been through the applicatio", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 94, "question": " OK, I will", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " Thanks, Sarah", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 98, "question": " Ill help you along the way since Ive already been through the applicatio", "qSentId": 97},{"answer": " No problem.  Call me at the end of this week", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 99, "question": " Thanks, Sarah", "qSentId": 98},{"answer": " OK.  Bye", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 100, "question": " No problem.  Call me at the end of this week", "qSentId": 99},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "04-01", "aSentId": 101, "question": " OK.  Bye", "qSentId": 100}]
